<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome. on toasters rocks</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome. on toasters rocks</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2020 J.P. Savard</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 22:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://toasters.rocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing a39.ca</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/a39/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/a39/</guid><description>Hey, been a while. 2021 was weird. Probably as much as 2020 was, and as much as 2022 probably will. I kind of took 2021 leisurely, mostly because of family illness, the Backstreet Boys Reunion Tour*, my day job, and helping family and friends that all took most of my time. I hope it gets better in 2022, so I kinda want to set some goals for now on.
Introducing here a39.</description></item><item><title>Toasters Rocks 4.0</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/toasters-rocks-4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 11:16:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/toasters-rocks-4/</guid><description>Well, it seems to be a tradition around this time of the year, every 368 days or so. A brand new blog. But this time, the story is quite interesting.
Genesis The first iteration of this blog was basically my Tumblr blog. By November 2018, I became largely disinterested by Tumblr due to various reasons, and I found this blog engine called WriteFreely, written in Go, could do federation so the blog posts would show up in people&amp;rsquo;s Mastodon feeds, effectively replicating some of Tumblr&amp;rsquo;s social features.</description></item><item><title>November updates</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/november-updates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 18:35:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/november-updates/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
First of all, thanks to our newest Patron, Terrence Wong, very appreciated :)
So I&amp;rsquo;m working on and off on this show bible for Zarmina, gathering pages of notes and failed scripts I wrote for myself into one concise document meant to show other people who dare help&amp;hellip; As I probably said in every post so far, the worst thing is motivation, I have a 9 to 5 job in the way and I have a family to care of, but eh, I&amp;rsquo;d say I&amp;rsquo;m half through the synopsis so far.</description></item><item><title>Zarmina updates</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-updates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 18:23:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-updates/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
Almost forgot I had a Patreon and someone is giving me a dollar a month, lol (thanks Pieman7373 :))
Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s some updates&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s been years I&amp;rsquo;m talking about Zarmina and not much came up out of it. I had some work done this summer, the outline of the story is now finally complete, and I now started writing a bible, organizing all my notes together so someone else can look at it and have a good idea of the whole picture.</description></item><item><title>Why is my OC a girl</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/why-is-my-oc-a-girl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/why-is-my-oc-a-girl/</guid><description>An OC, short for &amp;ldquo;original character&amp;rdquo;, is often used, especially in the brony and furry fandoms, as an avatar of oneself, and in those fandoms you&amp;rsquo;re encouraged to create one for yourself. And so is what I did as a brony around 2012, as a fan of My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic, this show that somehow went hugely popular outside its intended target audience due to being overly cute and wholesome, while not trying too much so the kids' parents could get behind as well.</description></item><item><title>I left social networks</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/i-left-social-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 20:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/i-left-social-networks/</guid><description>I have a love-hate relationship with Facebook and Twitter. On one hand, it&amp;rsquo;s a big forum with millions of people, all my friends are there, I meet new friends, they say some funny stuff, some cute stuff, I get all of my news there. It&amp;rsquo;s super useful to share my work, and to reach people who might like it. I love just saying randomly what&amp;rsquo;s on my mind for comedy, at the attention to whoever might hear it and find this funny.</description></item><item><title>Pandemic Story</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/pandemic-story/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 03:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/pandemic-story/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a bit of my life story. For starters, I&amp;rsquo;ve always had trouble finding a proper job, probably because I&amp;rsquo;m on the autism spectrum (of course, not something I&amp;rsquo;d like to explicitely tell everyone, for reasons), and/or I&amp;rsquo;ve had a very pelicular story on my resumé (in short, you know, the whole you need to have experience to have experience thing, the classic catch-22), I don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure. I&amp;rsquo;ve always worked freelance on some small projects with friends, friends of friends or for myself, comfortably at home, and I wanted to work in a big company that could provide me with a stable job and work in an office, for a change.</description></item><item><title>My Arch Linux packages: how to create your own repo</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/arch-linux-packages/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 07:41:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/arch-linux-packages/</guid><description>As I use Arch Linux as my daily driver on my main machine now and I use a lot the AUR nowadays (most notably I maintain the packages for The 8-Bit Guy&amp;rsquo;s Commander X16), figured I might create my own repository, right?
So there you go, after figuring it out on the Arch Wiki, here&amp;rsquo;s a collection of software I maintain on the AUR, some of my own things I bothered to make a PKGBUILD for, or just software not found in other binary repos I know the users of my communities will like.</description></item><item><title>Emoji region flags</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/emoji-region-flags/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 20:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/emoji-region-flags/</guid><description>&lt;p>For this project, I&amp;rsquo;ve been inspired by the &lt;a href="https://www.emoji.bzh">#emojibzh&lt;/a> movement which attempts to include the flag of the Brittany region of France in the emoji repertoire. So, I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at it and here&amp;rsquo;s what I found.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>King James Bible: An Adventure in Compression</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/king-james-bible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:38:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/king-james-bible/</guid><description>Well, time for another adventure, and with every adventure it begins with a very silly thought that isn&amp;rsquo;t even mine this time:
&amp;ldquo;I wonder if one can fit the entire bible on a TI-Nspire CX with mViewer GX PDF converter&amp;rdquo;, says our friend DJ
And there you go, am I searching for the answer:
me: trying to find out how big the Bible is in terms of computer storage because someone asked on Discord</description></item><item><title>Miyuki 2019</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/miyuki-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 01:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/miyuki-2019/</guid><description>Now this is a lot closer to the style I&amp;rsquo;m shooting for on Zarmina, which is now going to be a visual novel made in an actual visual novel engine, if you don&amp;rsquo;t know already. I love how it turned out: Minty Root suggested to make the lines thicker (that gives it a nice style), no shading (I think that adds to it), she now have a bow (although she isn&amp;rsquo;t gonna wear it until later in the story), the jewel is a bit more detailed (it&amp;rsquo;s a bitch to draw lol), her skirt is a bit shorter, boobs are a bit more, um, detailed (we&amp;rsquo;re shooting anime style after all!</description></item><item><title>Esoteric uses of CGI</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/esoteric-uses-of-cgi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 04:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/esoteric-uses-of-cgi/</guid><description>Well, you probably all heard of esoteric programming languages before, but the question today is, programming languages used outside its intended use, would that be esoteric?
If I tell you back-end web languages, you&amp;rsquo;d immediately think PHP, Node.js, Ruby, C maybe, but what if I tell you&amp;hellip; Commodore BASIC? Sure, just get a Commodore 64 with a TCP/IP stack and write a web server for it you&amp;rsquo;d say, but I mean, actually using it on an actual, everyday web server on some Linux box?</description></item><item><title>Horse Life 98</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/horse-life-98/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/horse-life-98/</guid><description>Been a while I wanted to make a webcomic, but I never got around at drawing one, and if I do I&amp;rsquo;m not that good at drawing, so&amp;hellip;
I recently started messing up with a Windows 98 VM (for various reasons, including a future redesign of this website), I re-discovered Microsoft Comic Chat, I decided to import my Pony Town avatars in it, and the rest is history. It&amp;rsquo;s simple to make, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take too much of my attention span and it looks good, so yeah, winning formula.</description></item><item><title>ecco the dolphin</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/ecco-the-dolphin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 02:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/ecco-the-dolphin/</guid><description>// Ecco effect v2 by juju2143 // based on original code by foone // https://github.com/foone/ecco-distortion-effect // Licenced under GPL3 var shifts = "gDkZcB510pQ:3pSf]4oLh\41pS;nWd_@lYcB5oT;nJ82pSfCkH7nVmWe^aA5110pO9nKh\bAlYdCkG7oL8nVe^a`@5oL82pSf\lXd^?lX=3oM9nV4oL9nVe^a`@"; function preload() { img = loadImage('/images/2019/11/background.png'); } function setup() { var c = createCanvas(320, 224); c.parent('sketch-holder'); } function draw() { for (var i = 0; i   Welcome to the second installment of my code experiments! This time we&amp;rsquo;re gonna look into the weird effect used in the background of messages in Ecco the Dolphin for the Sega Genesis (or MegaDrive, if you&amp;rsquo;re asking someone outside the Americas).</description></item><item><title>commissions</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/commissions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/commissions/</guid><description>You like this website? You wish to get a website just like this one to advertise your stuff? Super simple, not a pain to manage, tailored to your needs? Look no further, I can help you!
Included in the package:
Free hosting Custom theme You get control of everything Free training Domain name included Some guy with years of experience in internet things Contact me for a quote!</description></item><item><title>trippy perlin noise</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/trippy-perlin-noise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 18:16:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/trippy-perlin-noise/</guid><description>function setup() { var c = createCanvas(256, 256); c.parent('sketch-holder'); background(0); } function draw() { var n = 0; var z = 1; var speed = 0.005; noiseDetail(8, 0.65); loadPixels(); for(a=0; a  Now that I can easily embed JavaScript on this blog, I should put here some of my experiments and weird code that does nothing, cause why not. This one is some colored Perlin noise made using p5.</description></item><item><title>New blog, again</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/new-blog-again/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 07:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/new-blog-again/</guid><description>Yeah, I complain a lot about the fact I don&amp;rsquo;t write on my blog. I moved it again, this time on Ghost, after I found out I had free web hosting and it could run Node.js apps on it, so let&amp;rsquo;s try this. It was a bitch to install, though, as if Murphy&amp;rsquo;s law was playing against me. If it has a chance to fail, then it will fail. It took like 3 days, but I hope it&amp;rsquo;s worth it.</description></item><item><title>about me</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 06:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/about/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m J. P. Savard. (Obviously a pen name. Or is it?) Also known as Juju or Yuki.
I&amp;rsquo;m just a random freelance programmer from Québec City, Canada. I write things sometimes. It feels good.
Here you will find random musings about life, development logs, code experiments, educational content, or anything I deem worth to put on this silly blog. Might write in French sometimes, if you don&amp;rsquo;t understand, it might not concern you, look somewhere else.</description></item><item><title>Trailer is out</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/trailer-is-out/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 06:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/trailer-is-out/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Itch.io, reposting it here for completeness.
New trailer for the project, it&amp;rsquo;s not the complete game but I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll like it :) It&amp;rsquo;s been done with Ren&amp;rsquo;Py cause it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be the intro to the game and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to get a good video editing software working on my computer&amp;hellip; You can see it straight on the game&amp;rsquo;s page or if it&amp;rsquo;s buggy there&amp;rsquo;s a YouTube video.</description></item><item><title>DevLog #1: Making the trailer</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/devlog-1-making-the-trailer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/devlog-1-making-the-trailer/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
I told you I&amp;rsquo;m keeping you updated, so I&amp;rsquo;m keeping a dev log here on Patreon. Everything you need to know, so it sounds like I&amp;rsquo;m actually active at doing something and you can learn from my errors. Don&amp;rsquo;t want to decieve anyone who might want to throw money at me here.
First thing on my new plan is to post a trailer on YouTube, redirect people here and hope The Algorithm™ does its job somewhat soon.</description></item><item><title>Zarmina 3.0: rewrite (again)</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-3-0-rewrite-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-3-0-rewrite-again/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
This is a semi-Google Translation of the last post, for the English-speaking friends I might have here. I&amp;rsquo;m probably going to do this in both English and my native language that is French. Maybe also other languages too.
And that&amp;rsquo;s where I lost my motivation. Once again. I have not written anything since last winter, because, you see, I realized that it was not going anywhere in its current form.</description></item><item><title>April Fools 2019</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/april-fools-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/april-fools-2019/</guid><description>As usual, I like to prank people with good, original jokes on April 1st across my properties. Not these overused jokes everyone hates (for instance the local furry group deleted pranks because they were getting too much instances of the same overused, boring joke), but rather original and fun jokes. Or I try to, anyway. I didn&amp;rsquo;t took much effort and time doing any of them this year as I didn&amp;rsquo;t had any good ideas in advance, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t had time to do an elaborate one, but here&amp;rsquo;s a rundown of my pranks of this year.</description></item><item><title>Reflections on 2018, part 1: Writing a book</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/writing-a-book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/writing-a-book/</guid><description>So yeah. I&amp;rsquo;m writing a book. It&amp;rsquo;s called Zarmina. Pretty huge project I&amp;rsquo;m working on on and off for the last few years and it went through a bunch of iterations before what it is now&amp;hellip; I do believe that if you sit on a project for long enough, it&amp;rsquo;s going to evolve until it turns out pretty great. It&amp;rsquo;s still a pretty big undertaking and a very ambitious project, I rewrote the first part I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many times now under countless concepts and I procrastinated a lot of it, but I do think it&amp;rsquo;s turning out great.</description></item><item><title>How to thoroughly destroy spam accounts from Mastodon</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/how-to-thoroughly-destroy-spam-accounts-from-mastodon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/how-to-thoroughly-destroy-spam-accounts-from-mastodon/</guid><description>Well, it seems Mastodon have a problem with a particular spambot. As an instance admin, I investigated and here&amp;rsquo;s my findings.
Symptoms: Accounts keep singing up on your instance. The username are all random syllables (kind of sounds like Japanese), they have random full English/American-sounding names, their email address are all from random domains as if their owner have a pretty big budget on that and they all have different IPs.</description></item><item><title>Facebook sucks</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/facebook-sucks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/facebook-sucks/</guid><description>Well, I guess this thing will be a really nice place to vent. Because, allow me to say this, and I think everyone here will agree: Facebook sucks.
I mean, if you ever need to talk to their tech support to either change the name of your page, there&amp;rsquo;s a problem with it, or you even just want access to their API to integrate with your website (all true stories), let me get this straight, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a pain in the ass and take you months to get anywhere.</description></item><item><title>Toasters Rocks: The Reboot</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/toasters-rocks-the-reboot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/toasters-rocks-the-reboot/</guid><description>Yeah, let&amp;rsquo;s try this out, cause why not. It used to be Tumblr (which you can still follow here), but I recently switched to Write Freely, just to see how nicer it is. And looks like it works so far.
A while ago I realized I followed way too much people and it distracts me a lot from writing long texts, that and there was way too much NSFW to go there at school, so I kinda stopped going there.</description></item><item><title>Life update.</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/life-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/life-update/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Tumblr, reposting it here for completeness.
Well. I didn’t blogged that much in the past year or two on this toasters dot rocks blog, for some reason. My Tumblr timeline was looking like a disaster. Kinda like Facebook, actually, but that’s another kind of disaster. Oh well. I probably should blog a bit more and publish some texts I usually just condense in 280 characters on Twitter.</description></item><item><title>How to tell your AdBlock users to disable it like a boss</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/how-to-tell-your-adblock-users-to-disable-it-like-a-boss/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/how-to-tell-your-adblock-users-to-disable-it-like-a-boss/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Tumblr, reposting it here for completeness.
Boy, I don’t use Tumblr very often nowadays. Well, I wanted to write this article because, first of all, I hate ads and I know everyone else hates ads, myself I have uBlock with the anti-AdBlock killer on, but I also know people depends on it to make some good internet money and they want to do everything so their users can see the ads, even going as far as blocking the site’s content unless AdBlock is disabled… I have reasons to believe you’d piss these users off instead.</description></item><item><title>Those Create Your Taste Booths at McDonald’s</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/those-create-your-taste-booths-at-mcdonalds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/those-create-your-taste-booths-at-mcdonalds/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Tumblr, reposting it here for completeness.
You know what? I love those. They recently added some of them at the one in my town, pretty popular place after the summer festival taking place in Québec City each summer (we had the Red Hot Chili Peppers tonight, and tomorrow we’ll have Rammstein, so it’s pretty big). So yeah, after those shows the place is pretty crowded and no employee is getting a rest.</description></item><item><title>How to repost a video correctly on your social media page</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/how-to-repost-a-video-correctly-on-your-social-media-page/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/how-to-repost-a-video-correctly-on-your-social-media-page/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Tumblr, reposting it here for completeness.
Well, I usually don’t give a damn about this, but after seeing my good friend Minty Root allegedly being butthurt over this and seeing a GIF of his work being (re)posted on Facebook without credit, it stroke me, and I figured I had a good argument about this.
For this post, I’ll use Minty as an example here, because I know how he’s set up on YouTube, but it works for most, if not all content creators out there.</description></item></channel></rss>