<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Zarmina on toasters rocks</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/tags/zarmina/</link><description>Recent content in Zarmina on toasters rocks</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2020 J.P. Savard</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 18:35:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://toasters.rocks/tags/zarmina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>November updates</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/november-updates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 18:35:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/november-updates/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
First of all, thanks to our newest Patron, Terrence Wong, very appreciated :)
So I&amp;rsquo;m working on and off on this show bible for Zarmina, gathering pages of notes and failed scripts I wrote for myself into one concise document meant to show other people who dare help&amp;hellip; As I probably said in every post so far, the worst thing is motivation, I have a 9 to 5 job in the way and I have a family to care of, but eh, I&amp;rsquo;d say I&amp;rsquo;m half through the synopsis so far.</description></item><item><title>Zarmina updates</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-updates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 18:23:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-updates/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
Almost forgot I had a Patreon and someone is giving me a dollar a month, lol (thanks Pieman7373 :))
Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s some updates&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s been years I&amp;rsquo;m talking about Zarmina and not much came up out of it. I had some work done this summer, the outline of the story is now finally complete, and I now started writing a bible, organizing all my notes together so someone else can look at it and have a good idea of the whole picture.</description></item><item><title>Miyuki 2019</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/miyuki-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 01:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/miyuki-2019/</guid><description>Now this is a lot closer to the style I&amp;rsquo;m shooting for on Zarmina, which is now going to be a visual novel made in an actual visual novel engine, if you don&amp;rsquo;t know already. I love how it turned out: Minty Root suggested to make the lines thicker (that gives it a nice style), no shading (I think that adds to it), she now have a bow (although she isn&amp;rsquo;t gonna wear it until later in the story), the jewel is a bit more detailed (it&amp;rsquo;s a bitch to draw lol), her skirt is a bit shorter, boobs are a bit more, um, detailed (we&amp;rsquo;re shooting anime style after all!</description></item><item><title>Trailer is out</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/trailer-is-out/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 06:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/trailer-is-out/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Itch.io, reposting it here for completeness.
New trailer for the project, it&amp;rsquo;s not the complete game but I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll like it :) It&amp;rsquo;s been done with Ren&amp;rsquo;Py cause it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be the intro to the game and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to get a good video editing software working on my computer&amp;hellip; You can see it straight on the game&amp;rsquo;s page or if it&amp;rsquo;s buggy there&amp;rsquo;s a YouTube video.</description></item><item><title>DevLog #1: Making the trailer</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/devlog-1-making-the-trailer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/devlog-1-making-the-trailer/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
I told you I&amp;rsquo;m keeping you updated, so I&amp;rsquo;m keeping a dev log here on Patreon. Everything you need to know, so it sounds like I&amp;rsquo;m actually active at doing something and you can learn from my errors. Don&amp;rsquo;t want to decieve anyone who might want to throw money at me here.
First thing on my new plan is to post a trailer on YouTube, redirect people here and hope The Algorithm™ does its job somewhat soon.</description></item><item><title>Zarmina 3.0: rewrite (again)</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-3-0-rewrite-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/zarmina-3-0-rewrite-again/</guid><description>This article was originally published on Patreon, reposting it here for completeness.
This is a semi-Google Translation of the last post, for the English-speaking friends I might have here. I&amp;rsquo;m probably going to do this in both English and my native language that is French. Maybe also other languages too.
And that&amp;rsquo;s where I lost my motivation. Once again. I have not written anything since last winter, because, you see, I realized that it was not going anywhere in its current form.</description></item><item><title>Reflections on 2018, part 1: Writing a book</title><link>http://toasters.rocks/writing-a-book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://toasters.rocks/writing-a-book/</guid><description>So yeah. I&amp;rsquo;m writing a book. It&amp;rsquo;s called Zarmina. Pretty huge project I&amp;rsquo;m working on on and off for the last few years and it went through a bunch of iterations before what it is now&amp;hellip; I do believe that if you sit on a project for long enough, it&amp;rsquo;s going to evolve until it turns out pretty great. It&amp;rsquo;s still a pretty big undertaking and a very ambitious project, I rewrote the first part I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many times now under countless concepts and I procrastinated a lot of it, but I do think it&amp;rsquo;s turning out great.</description></item></channel></rss>