<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rant on toasters rocks</title>
    <link>http://toasters.rocks/tags/rant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rant on toasters rocks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020 J.P. Savard</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://toasters.rocks/tags/rant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why is my OC a girl</title>
      <link>http://toasters.rocks/why-is-my-oc-a-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://toasters.rocks/why-is-my-oc-a-girl/</guid>
      <description>An OC, short for &amp;ldquo;original character&amp;rdquo;, is often used, especially in the brony and furry fandoms, as an avatar of oneself, and in those fandoms you&amp;rsquo;re encouraged to create one for yourself. And so is what I did as a brony around 2012, as a fan of My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic, this show that somehow went hugely popular outside its intended target audience due to being overly cute and wholesome, while not trying too much so the kids&#39; parents could get behind as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Story</title>
      <link>http://toasters.rocks/pandemic-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 03:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://toasters.rocks/pandemic-story/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a bit of my life story. For starters, I&amp;rsquo;ve always had trouble finding a proper job, probably because I&amp;rsquo;m on the autism spectrum (of course, not something I&amp;rsquo;d like to explicitely tell everyone, for reasons), and/or I&amp;rsquo;ve had a very pelicular story on my resumé (in short, you know, the whole you need to have experience to have experience thing, the classic catch-22), I don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure. I&amp;rsquo;ve always worked freelance on some small projects with friends, friends of friends or for myself, comfortably at home, and I wanted to work in a big company that could provide me with a stable job and work in an office, for a change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook sucks</title>
      <link>http://toasters.rocks/facebook-sucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://toasters.rocks/facebook-sucks/</guid>
      <description>Well, I guess this thing will be a really nice place to vent. Because, allow me to say this, and I think everyone here will agree: Facebook sucks.
I mean, if you ever need to talk to their tech support to either change the name of your page, there&amp;rsquo;s a problem with it, or you even just want access to their API to integrate with your website (all true stories), let me get this straight, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a pain in the ass and take you months to get anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Those Create Your Taste Booths at McDonald’s</title>
      <link>http://toasters.rocks/those-create-your-taste-booths-at-mcdonalds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://toasters.rocks/those-create-your-taste-booths-at-mcdonalds/</guid>
      <description>This article was originally published on Tumblr, reposting it here for completeness.
You know what? I love those. They recently added some of them at the one in my town, pretty popular place after the summer festival taking place in Québec City each summer (we had the Red Hot Chili Peppers tonight, and tomorrow we’ll have Rammstein, so it’s pretty big). So yeah, after those shows the place is pretty crowded and no employee is getting a rest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
